Hello developers! Are you tired of daily issue management?
こんにちは。開発者の皆さん、 毎日のIssue対応に疲れていませんか？
Miyabi is a fully autonomous development framework that automatically writes code, runs tests,
Miyabiは、GitHub Issueを投げるだけで、 AIが自動的にコードを書き、テストを実行し、
and creates Pull Requests - just by creating a GitHub Issue.
Pull Requestを作成する、 完全自律型の開発フレームワークです。
Today, I'll show you the power of Miyabi in just 3 minutes.
今日は、わずか3分でMiyabiの魅力を お見せします。
Installation is incredibly simple.
インストールは驚くほど簡単です。
First, install Rust. Then, clone Miyabi,
まず、Rustをインストールします。 次に、Miyabiをクローンして、
and run cargo build.
cargo buildを実行するだけ。
That's it! 21 specialized agents join your development team.
たったこれだけで、21個の専門Agentが あなたの開発チームに加わります。
Let's see it in action.
では、実際の動作を見てみましょう。
We create Issue #270: "Enable TypeScript strict mode"
Issue #270: 「TypeScript strict mode 有効化」 というIssueを作成します。
Then, we run just one command: miyabi work-on 270
次に、たった一つのコマンドを実行します。 miyabi work-on 270
Four specialized agents start working in sequence.
すると、4つの専門Agentが順番に動き出します。
First, "Coordinator" decomposes the task.
まず、「しきるん」がタスクを分解します。
Then, "CodeGen" implements the code.
次に、「つくるん」がコードを実装します。
Next, "Review" checks the quality.
そして、「めだまん」が品質をチェックします。
Finally, "PR" creates the Pull Request.
最後に、「まとめるん」が Pull Requestを作成します。
In just 10 minutes, a review-ready PR is complete.
わずか10分で、レビュー可能な状態のPRが 完成しました。
Miyabi includes 21 unique specialized agents.
Miyabiには、21個のユニークな 専門Agentがいます。
The coding team consists of: Coordinator - Task orchestration
コーディングチームには： しきるん - タスク統括
CodeGen - Code generation Review - Quality review
つくるん - コード生成 めだまん - 品質レビュー
Issue - Issue analysis PR - Pull request creation
みつけるん - Issue分析 まとめるん - PR作成
Deployment - Deployment automation Refresher - State monitoring
はこぶん - デプロイ つなぐん - 状態監視
Additionally, the business team has 14 agents automating everything from strategic planning
さらに、ビジネスチームには14個のAgentが、 戦略立案からマーケティング、営業まで、
to marketing and sales.
あらゆる業務を自動化します。
With Miyabi, your team's productivity improves dramatically.
Miyabiを使えば、あなたのチームの生産性は 劇的に向上します。
From issue creation to deployment, fully automated.
Issue作成からデプロイまで、完全自動化。
Developers can focus on truly important decisions.
開発者は、本当に重要な意思決定に 集中できます。
Miyabi is completely open source.
Miyabiは、完全オープンソース。
Star us on GitHub and start for free today.
今すぐGitHubでスターをつけて、 無料で始めましょう。
Ready to revolutionize your development workflow?
あなたの開発ワークフローを、 今日から革新しませんか？
Thank you for watching!
ご視聴ありがとうございました。